Li Xing

E-mail: polairslee1984@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexdevman/

Skype: polairslee1984 Weixin: polarislee1984

Profile:

Full stack developer/architect/Team Leader.

I have 15+ years development experience with web/app/backend/solutions.

From small project to large one, I attended as developer, architect and PM etc and carry out too many project successfully.

Last a few years, i built and leaded several projects such as ERP, MES, Travel booking and delivery system etc.

Also I had developed several mobile apps and web apps too.

I'm looking forward to long-term remote development task.

Skills Summary:

- C/C++/C#
- Php, Laravel
- Golang
- NodeJS
- Python
- JAVA/J2EE
- ASP.NET
- AngularJS/ReactJS/VueJS
- Electron App Development
- Objective C
- Android Java
- React Native Mobile
- HTML5/CSS3/Javascript
- Oracle/MySQL/MSSQL/Postgre/MongoDB

Qualifications:

Master's Degree of Computer Science CCNA Certification

Languages:

Chinese, English

Education:

- 2001 2006 Beijing Information Science & Technology University, Computer Science
- 2006 2008 Beijing Information Science & Technology University, Computer Science (Master's Degree)
- 2009 OOP Developer Course
- 2012 OOP PM Course
- 2014 CCNA Training Course

Employment History:

Nova China, China

S/W Architect/Engineer

2012 - 2015

- DLP Solution Development(Windows Kernel Driver/C++)
- IPTV Service Platform Development(Java/J2EE, iOS/Android)
- Cambodia Network Center S/W Group Development(NMS, TMS, DMS, SMS)
- ETL Solution Development(Java/SWT)

Neusis, USA(Remote)

Web/Mobile Developer

2016-2017

- Tommy Now, Tommy Snipsnap, Roar for us, Milkcrate App development(React Native, Unity)
- Video CMS Development(AngularJS/Php)
- Cloud File Sharing Solution Development(Electron)

Room-Res, Australia(Remote)

S/W Architect/Engineer

2018-2020

Hotel Booking Service Development(React JS, PHP, golang)

ShengTianYang, China

S/W Team Leader/Architect

2017-

- Transport Delivery System(Angular, Nodejs)
- Skycoin Backend/Admin Panel Development(golang, angularJS)
- MES System development(golang, reactJS)
- ERP System development(ASP.NET, ReactJS)
- SCADA System(Java/C++)
- Blockchain based web/solution development such as coin development, mining, exchange platform, presell service, gaming and other services
- Doctor Web Portal(Laravel)
- Job Seeking Portal(Angular 7)